Register of the Institute of Economic Affairs (Great Britain) records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Arthur Seldon File, 1941-1987
  - Speeches and writings
    - "Income Tax: It Can Be Cut," Daily Telegraph Magazine, printed copy and correspondence. Includes letters from readers, 1969 March 28 (Folder 29)
    - "Pubs and Alcoholics," letter to the editor, Times, typescript and correspondence, 1969 April 30 (Folder 30)
    - "In the Public Interest...?" Daily Telegraph Magazine, typescript and correspondence, 1969 May (Folder 31)
    - "Explaining the Free Market Economy," lecture, Internationale Konferenz marktwirtschaftlicher Organisationen/4th International Conference of Organisations for Market Economy, Biel (Switzerland), 1969 May 8 (Box 343)
      - General (Folder 1)
        Program, synopsis of study by W. Frickhöffer [?], papers by R. Eibel and L. Erhard, and correspondence.
      - Typescript of synopsis, typescripts, and printed copy (Zeitfragen No. 96, 1969 November (Folder 2)
    - "How to End the Pensions Pickle," Sunday Telegraph, printed copy, 1969 May 25 (Folder 3)
    - "Whose Obedient Servant?" Daily Telegraph Magazine, printed copy, 1969 June 13 (Folder 4)
    - "Time to Roll Back the State," Daily Telegraph, Correspondence, 1969 July 8 (Folder 5)
    - "Mr. Crossman's Dilemma," Daily Telegraph, printed copy, 1969 October 2 (Folder 6)
    - "Pensions Pie in the Sky," Sunday Telegraph, printed copy, 1969 November 9 (Folder 7)
    - "Paying for Social Services," letter to the editor, Times, galleys and correspondence, 1969 December (Folder 8)
    - The Great Pensions "Swindle,", 1970
      See also Correspondence/Buchanan, James and Colin Campbell.
      - Typescript of draft and statement (Folder 9)
      - "The Great Pension Swindle," outline and advertisement of the book by Arthur Seldon, Daily Telegraph, printed copy, 1970 February 5 (Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, 1969 January - 1971 May (Folder 11)
        Includes Tom Stacey Books brochures and reviews.
    - "Selectivity," speech, Fabian Society, Beatrice Webb House, Caster [?], notes, 1970 (Box 344, Folder 1)
    - "The Compassion Fashion," Daily Telegraph Magazine, typescript and correspondence, 1970 February 27 (Folder 2)
    - "Preparing Men for Manhood," speech ?, notes, 1970 March 14 (Folder 3)
    - "BBC Bias" letter to the editor, Daily Telegraph, typescript, printed copy, and correspondence, 1970 April 4 (Folder 4)
    - "Paying for Health," letter to the editor, Times, typescript and correspondence, 1970 April 30 (Folder 5)
    - "One Standard or Two?" letter to the editor, The Lancet, printed copy, 1970 May 16 (Folder 6)
    - "Another Source of Finance," letter to the editor, British Hospital Journal and Social Service Review, printed copy and correspondence. See also Editorial, undated, 1970 May 29 (Folder 7)
    - "The Wasteful Welfare State," letter to the editor, Daily Telegraph, printed copy, 1970 June 5 (Folder 8)
    - "Economic Strategy 1970-1974/75: Four and a Half Years to De-Fuse Socialism," Aide memoire, Typescript, 1970 June 21 (Folder 9)
    - "Bring Welfare into the Market," Daily Telegraph, printed copy, 1970 July 31 (Folder 10)
    - "Tax Cuts Now to De-Fuse Socialism," Sunday Telegraph, correspondence, 1970 August 23 (Folder 11)
    - "A Time Now for Self-Help," Daily Telegraph, printed copy, 1970 October 8 (Folder 12)
    - "Who Is Dividing the Nation?" Daily Telegraph, printed copy, 1970 December 16 (Folder 13)
    - "Self-Help and the State," speech, CPC Ashford, typescript, 1971 February 20 (Folder 14)
    - "Why Not Top up the Poor Man's Pay?" Daily Telegraph, printed copy, 1971 February 22 (Folder 15)
    - "The Next Step in Social Policy," speech, Conservative Backbench, Social Security Committee, Notes and clipping, 1971 March 10 (Folder 16)
    - "Rise Not All Pensioners Need" and "The Moral Claim to a Retirement Pension," letters to the editor, Daily Telegraph, Printed copies and correspondence, 1971 March 29 and May 4 (Folder 17)
      Includes letters from newspaper readers.
    - "Pensions, the Budget and Government," speech, Thames Valley Life and Pensions Society annual general meeting, Holograph and typescript of press release, 1971 April 7 (Folder 18)
    - "Fares for the Old," letter to the editor, Times, Typescript, printed copy, and correspondence, 1971 April 13 (Folder 19)
    - "Playing Put and Take with Taxes," Daily Telegraph, Typescript, printed copy, and correspondence, 1971 April 23 (Folder 20)
    - "Pensions, Politicians and Pundits," Spectator, typescript and correspondence, 1971 June (Folder 21)
    - "Self-Help in the Seventies," Sunday Times, typescript, 1971 June (Folder 22)
    - "Politically Impossible...? Hutt versus Butler," Sunday Telegraph, notes and correspondence, 1971 July 5 (Folder 23)
    - "Reverse Taxes to Abolish Poverty," Daily Telegraph, typescript, printed copy, and correspondence, 1971 July 15 (Folder 24)
    - "Time to Review Art of Politically Possible," Glasgow Herald, printed copy, 1971 August 9 (Folder 25)
    - "Entrusting Democracy to Politicians," Swinton Journal, printed copy, 1971 autumn (Folder 26)
    - "Two Cheers for Tory Pensions," Sunday Telegraph, typescript, printed copy, and printed note, 1971 September 19 (Folder 27)
    - "The New Tory Welfare State," Daily Telegraph, notes, printed copy, and correspondence, 1971 October 15 (Folder 28)
    - "Poverty," New Society, printed copy, 1971 October 21 (Folder 29)
    - "American Source for the N.H.S. Gander," [Daily?] Telegraph, mailing list, 1971 December 1 (Folder 30)
    - "Crueller than Unemployment," Daily Telegraph, notes, correspondence, and mailing list, 1972 January 31 (Folder 31)
    - "Health Through Profit," Daily Telegraph Magazine, typescript and correspondence, 1972 January (Folder 32)
    - "Myths and Waste of Welfare," Sunday Telegraph, printed copy, correspondence, and mailing list, 1972 January 9 (Folder 33)
    - Letter to the editor, Daily Telegraph, typescript and clipping, 1972 January 14 (Folder 34)
    - "Bring Bureaucrats to Book," Daily Telegraph, notes, correspondence and clippings, 1972 January 17 (Folder 35)
    - "LPA Bureaucracy," Daily Telegraph, galleys and correspondence, 1972 February (Box 345, Folder 1)
    - Letter to the editor, Financial Times, typescript and correspondence, 1972 March 12 (Folder 2)
    - Letter to the editor, Daily Telegraph, typescript, 1972 March 20 (Folder 3)
    - "The Education Rut: The Voucher Way out," Financial Times, Typescript and correspondence, 1972 May (Folder 4)
    - "The Private Health Service," Daily Telegraph, printed copy, 1972 May 11 (Folder 5)
    - "The Conservatives and the Welfare State," Crossbow, Correspondence, 1972 [August] (Folder 6)
    - Foreword to the Annual Report of the Birmingham and Midland Counties Wholesale Brewers' Association, Off-print, 1972 December 31 (Folder 7)
    - "I.E.A. and E.E.C.," Uniropa, typescript and correspondence, 1973 (Folder 8)
    - "Time to Shore Up the Family," Daily Telegraph, correspondence, 1973 March 8 (Folder 9)
    - "Why We Should Let Europe Destroy Our Welfare State," Sunday Times, printed copy and correspondence, 1973 June 3 (Folder 10)
    - Letter to the editor, Times, typescript and background material, 1973 December (Folder 11)
    - World Medical Care [published studies on the situation in different countries, edited by A. Seldon. Typescripts. See also Subject file/International Federation of Voluntary Health Service Funds/Letter to O'Mahony, 1973 June 13
      - General, contents table and lists of contributors (Folder 12)
      - "World Medical Care" by Arthur Seldon, preface, 1972 August 15 (Folder 13)
      - Introduction (Folder 14)
      - Austria (Folder 15)
      - Belgium (Folder 16)
      - Canada (Folder 17)
      - Denmark (Folder 18)
      - East European countries (Folder 19)
      - Finland (Folder 20)
      - France (Folder 21)
      - Germany (Box 346, Folder 1)
      - Great Britain (Folder 2)
        Includes study entitled "Private Expenditure as a Source of Finance for Medical Care in Britain" by Arthur Seldon.
      - Ireland (Folder 3)
      - Italy (Folder 4)
      - Japan (Folder 5)
      - Luxembourg (Folder 6)
      - Netherlands and Belgium (Folder 7)
      - New Zealand (Folder 8)
      - Norway (Folder 9)
      - Sweden (Folder 10)
      - Switzerland (Folder 11)
      - United States (Box 347, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous (Folder 2)
        Includes loose typescript pages, notes, and unidentified appendix.
    - "How Much Longer Welfare State?" Mont Pèlerin Society meeting, Brussels (Belgium), typescript, 1974 (Folder 3)
    - Plant, Arnold, Selected Economic Essays and Addresses, Edited and with a foreword by Arthur Seldon, 1974
      - Manuscript (Folder 4)
        Typescript of Arthur Seldon's passages (incomplete) and printed copies of Arnold Plant's papers.
      - Correspondence
        - 1969-1972 (Folder 5)
        - 1973 (Folder 6)
        - 1974-1977 (Box 348, Folder 1)
    - Letter to the editor, Daily Telegraph, typescript and correspondence, 1974 December 11 (Folder 2)
    - "Morality of the N.H.S.," lecture, notes and correspondence, 1975 January 15 (Folder 3)
    - "Local Government: Problem of Finance," letter to the editor, 1975 April 9 (Folder 4)
      See also Speeches and Writings / Charge, 1977 / Preliminary introduction and chapters I-X.
    - "Mr. Healey and Government Spending," letter to the editor, 1975 June 13 (Folder 5)
    - "Capitalism and the Historians," Mont Pèlerin Society meeting, Hillsdale (U.S.A.), 1975 August (Folder 6)
    - "Market or Government," letter to the editor, 1975 September (Folder 7)
    - Letter to the editor, Times, typescript and correspondence, 1975 September 27 (Folder 8)
    - "Prof. F. G. Pennance," obituary, Daily Telegraph, typescript and printed copy, 1975 October 14 (Folder 9)
    - "Equality Fallacy in the N.H.S.," letter to the editor, Daily Telegraph, printed copy, 1975 October 21 (Folder 10)
    - "The National Health: A Suitable Case for Freedom," Evening Standard, printed copy, 1975 October 29 (Folder 11)
    - "'Sorry - I'm Sending Him to Another School,'" Evening Standard, printed copy, 1975 November 18 (Folder 12)
    - "Vouchers to Restore the Missing Link in Education," Conservative Monthly News: Open Forum, typescript and correspondence, 1975 December (Folder 13)
    - "The Market in Ideas: A Comment," Mont Pèlerin Society meeting, Paris (France), 1976 January 17
      - Typescript and correspondence (Folder 14-15)
      - Conference papers and brochures
    - "Your Money and Your Life," Daily Express, [?], typescript, 1976 March (Folder 16)
    - "Layfield: Why Not Charge for Services?" Municipal Review, typescript, printed copy, and correspondence, 1976 July (Folder 17)
    - "Galbraith or Economic Freedom," preface, Milton Friedman, From Galbraith to Economic Freedom, 1976-1977
      See PUBLICATIONS/Manuscripts/Occasional Papers/No. 49.
    - Charge, 1977 (Box 349)
      - Typescripts
        - No. 1
          - Preliminary introduction (two first pages missing), contents, and note on the author. Includes printed copy of two letters to the editor ("Local Government: Problem of Finance" and "State Aid at a Price"), Times (Folder 1)
          - Chapters I-X (Folder 2)
          - Tables and appendices (Folder 3)
          - Abridged alphabetical index (Folder 4)
        - No. 2. Chapters I-IV (Folder 5)
        - No. 3
          - Chapters I-IV, X and XIII (Folder 6)
          - Miscellaneous (Folder 7)
            Includes addendum and tables.
      - Corrected script and proofs with tables (incomplete) (Folder 8-9)
      - Advertisements, text for dust jacket [?], and notices [by Arthur Seldon ?], 1977 (Box 350, Folder 1)
        Includes typescripts and printed copies of his articles "Do the British Want a Police State?" Times, "How the State Has Tied Us in Knots," Sunday Times, and "Would You Like Half Your Taxes Back?" Daily Express.
      - Reviews (Folder 2)
      - Correspondence
        - General
          - A-F (Folder 3)
          - G-L (Folder 4)
            Includes correspondence with Milton Friedman.
          - M-R (Folder 5)
          - S-Y (Folder 6)
        - Re publication
          - Readers (Eric Sharp and C. H. Houghton of Sowerby) (Folder 7)
          - Temple Smith, Maurice (publisher) (Folder 8)
        - Re distribution (Box 351)
          - General (address lists and sample letters) (Folder 1)
          - Among I.E.A. dinner guests, [?], 1978 May (Folder 2)
          - House of Commons members (Folder 3-4)
        - Miscellaneous (Folder 5)
          Includes invoices and order forms.
    - "How the State Has Tied Us in Knots," Sunday Times, 1977 November 13
      See Speeches and writings/Charge, 1977/Advertisements, cover text, and notices.
    - "Would You Like Half Your Taxes Back?" Daily Express, 1977
      See Speeches and writings/ Charge, 1977/Advertisements, cover text, and notices.
    - "Evidence to the Royal Commission on the National Health Service" (with Ralph Harris), 1977 February (Folder 6)
      See Subject file/Center for Policy Studies: Health Study Group.
    - Letter to the editor, Daily Telegraph, typescript, 1977 March 7 (Box 352, Folder 1)
    - "The Liberal Teacher Who Turned His Back on Old Age to Lead World Thought," Times, printed copy, 1977 May 9 (Folder 2)
    - "Who Do You Want to Run Your Life: State or Market?" Daily Telegraph, printed copy and correspondence, 1977 August 26 (Folder 3)
    - "Do the British Want a Police State?" Times, 1977 September
      See Charge, 1977/Advertisements and notices.
    - "The Policeman's Dilemma: How far Is Security a Public Service?" Top Security International, typescript, printed copy and correspondence, 1977 December (Folder 4)
      See also Correspondence/British Security Industry Association.
    - The Coming Confrontation: Will the Open Society Survive to 1989?, 1978
      Edited and including a paper by Arthur Seldon. See PUBLICATIONS/ Manuscripts/Hobart Paperbacks/No. 12.
    - "What Every Economist Ought to Know," (with Ralph Harris), Sunday Telegraph, typescript, 1978 January 25 (Folder 5)
    - "Hail, a Male Thatcher," Free Nation, printed copy, 1978 May 26 -June 8 (Folder 6)
    - "Education Vouchers: A Symbol of Western 'Pluralism,'" Times, printed copy, 1978 June 6 (Folder 7)
    - "Local Government Finance," letter to the editor, Times, printed copy, 1978 August 17 (Folder 8)
    - "Can the Family Afford Rich Uncle Jim's Charity?" Daily Telegraph, printed copy, 1978 October 2 (Folder 9)
    - Letter to the editor, Reader's Digest, incomplete holograph and correspondence, 1978 [November?] (Folder 10)
    - "Put the Townhall in Its Place," Evening Standard, 1978 December 28
      See Correspondence/Wright, Roy (Evening Standard).
    - "The British Turn to Cut Taxes. Margaret Thatcher's New Economic Policy: Hopes and Vistas,", 1979
      See Correspondence/Institute for Contemporary Studies.
    - "Higher Taxes or Deteriorating Services: A Third Way?," Observer, typescript and correspondence, 1979 (Folder 11)
    - "Individual Liberty, Public Goods and Representative Democracy: Lessons from the West and Escape for the East," [Festschrift f¨r F. A. von Hayek zum 80. Geburtstag], Ordo XXX, typescript, printed copy, and correspondence, 1979 (Folder 12)
    - Over-Ruled on Welfare (with Ralph Harris [HPB 13]), 1979 (Folder 13)
      Typescript of the exposé entitled "Was the Welfare State Really Necessary?" Includes advertising text by Antony Flew.
    - Preface to the 2nd edition of Samuel Brittan's Participation without Politics (Hobart 62), typescript, 1979
      See Correspondence/Brittan, Samuel.
    - "Crying Wolf," Daily Telegraph, typescript and correspondence, 1979 January 17 (Folder 14)
    - "Why Leave the Rubbish to the Council Men?" Evening Standard, printed copy and reader's response, 1979 February 12 (Folder 15)
    - "Let Parents Really Choose," Daily Telegraph, typescript, printed copy, and correspondence, 1979 May (Folder 16)
    - Letter to the editor, Daily Telegraph, typescript, 1979 June 20 (Folder 17)
    - "Getting Rid of State Education and National Health," interview, British Broadcasting Corporation, typescript, 1979 June 28 (Folder 18)
    - "Salaries in Civil Service," letter to the editor, Daily Telegraph, printed copy and correspondence, 1979 July 23 (Folder 19)
    - "The Inevitability of Confrontation," Sunday Telegraph, typescript, 1979 July 25 (Folder 20)
    - Reaction to the report of the Royal Commission on the National Health Service, The Lancet, printed copy, 1979 July 28 (Folder 21)
      See also Subject file/Centre for Policy Studies.
    - Letter to the editor, Evening Standard, typescript, 1979 July 30 (Folder 22)
    - "When the Squealing Has to Stop," Daily Mail, typescript and correspondence, circa 1979 August (Folder 23)
    - "National Health Disservice," Daily Telegraph, printed copy, 1979 August 2 (Folder 24)
    - "State or Market: Have We a Choice?" (with Ralph Harris), Guardian, Typescript and correspondence, 1979 August 6 (Folder 25)
    - "You Pay Your Money, Who Makes Your Choice?" (together with R. Harris), Guardian, 1979, 1987 (Folder 26)
      Galleys of excerpt to be republished in Economics Explained and correspondence.
    - "Health and the Poor Man," typescript, 1979 August 16
      See Litmus Papers, 1980/Background material.
    - "Consumers in the Welfare Market," letter to the editor, Guardian, typescript, 1979 August 22 (Folder 27)
    - "How to Increase Wealth without Working Harder," The News of the World, typescript and correspondence, 1979 August 22 (Folder 28)
    - "Women Rule: O.K?," Crossbow, typescript and printed copy, 1979 Autumn (Folder 29)
    - "Bigger Cuts... Better Schools" (with Marjorie Seldon), Free Nation, typescript and printed copy, 1979 September 14-27 (Folder 30)
    - "Phase out the Civil Servants," Daily Telegraph, printed copy and correspondence, 1979 October 5 (Box 353, Folder 1)
      Includes letter to Friedrich A. von Hayek.
    - "Corrigible Capitalism, Specious Socialism," talk, Center for Human Ecology, Edinburgh University, 1979 October 9 (Folder 2)
      Includes notes, typescript, correspondence, brochures and papers. Includes correspondence with and papers by John A. Loraine.
    - "Britain: Economic Decline," lecture, Monday Club, 1979 October 17 (Folder 3)
    - "The Price of Local Democracy Is a Service Charge," Daily Telegraph, typescript, printed copy, and correspondence, 1979 November 20 (Folder 4)
    - Lecture, Bath, notes, 1979 November 22 (Folder 5)
    - Lecture, Cumberland Lodge, Windsor, notes and correspondence, 1979 November 24 (Folder 6)
    - Lecture, Cardiff, 1979 November 29
      Typed notes and flyer. See "Aux Armes, Citoyens".
    - "It's Time to Cut Down the Weeds...," Daily Mail, printed copy, 1979 November 30 (Folder 7)
    - "Cut Now - and Cut Boldly," Daily Telegraph, typescript, printed copy, and correspondence, 1979 December 21 (Folder 8)
    - Chapter 4, with Cotton M. Lindsay, New Directions in Public Health Care: A Prescription for the 1980s (Folder 9)
      Notes and correspondence. See also Correspondence/Institute for Contemporary Studies (A. Lawrence Chickering).
    - Concluding essay, Cotton M. Lindsay, National Health Issues: The British Experience, correspondence, 1980
      - General (Folder 10)
      - Lindsay, Cotton M. (Folder 11)
        Includes review of the book in The Times.
      - Murley, Reginald (Folder 12)
      - Roche Laboratories (Folder 13)
      - Taylor of Harlow (Folder 14)
    - "Cut Taxes and Damn the Bureaucracy," Sunday Times, typescript and correspondence, 1979 December 27 (Folder 15)
    - "A Better Way to Pay for Medicine," NOW!, typescript and correspondence, 1980 (Folder 16)
    - Corrigible Capitalism, Incorrigible Socialism, 1980
      See Correspondence/Heritage Foundation.
    - The Litmus Papers: A National Health Dis-Service, edited and with contributions by A. Seldon, 1980
      - Background material, 1979 August 16 (Folder 17)
        Clippings and typescript of Arthur Seldon's article "Health and the Poor Man".
      - Biographical notes of essayists (Folder 18)
      - Galleys of A. Seldon's contributions: "The N.H.S.: Success? Still on trial? Failure?" and "The N.H.S. Is Inadequate for Industry and Trade Unions." Includes typescript of his articles "Why We Need a Free Market in Health," "Italy: Warned in Time?," "Why the NHS Must Fail,", 1980 (Folder 19)
      - Reviews (Box 354)
        - General, mostly press cuttings (Folder 1)
        - Re Charles Hall's review in Health Services Manpower Review, correspondence
          - Hall, Charles (Folder 2)
          - Essayists et al. (Folder 3)
      - Correspondence
        - With essayists
          - General, list of potential contributors and initial letter to them (Folder 4)
          - Included in final publication
            - Anderson, Digby C. (Folder 5)
            - Jewkes, John (Folder 6)
            - Jones, Ivor (Folder 7)
            - Juby, Bernard A., includes synopsis and article by him (Folder 8)
            - Lait, June (Folder 9)
            - Lindsay, Cotton M. (Folder 10)
            - Moncrieff, Andrew (Folder 11)
            - Noble, John S. (Folder 12)
            - Piggott, Francis (Folder 13)
            - Reekie, Duncan (Folder 14)
            - Sherman, Alfred (Folder 15)
            - Smith, David (Folder 16)
            - Wood, Patrick (Folder 17)
          - Not included in final publication (refused or declined) (Folder 18)
        - Kirwan, Patricia (publishing consultant, Centre for Policy Studies) (Folder 19)
        - Miscellaneous re distribution (Folder 20)
      - Miscellaneous clippings, unidentified typed notes, and typed notes by Arthur Seldon (Folder 21)
    - "The Private Pocket, Not the Public Purse, Is the Best Defense Against Runaway Inflation" (with R. Harris et al.), open memorandum to Mrs. Thatcher and Mr. Callaghan, Times, typescript, printed copy, and correspondence, 1980 January 9 (Folder 22)
    - "The Conservative Left Ethos of British Higher Education," Times Higher Education Supplement, correspondence and clippings, 1980 January 25 (Folder 23)
      Includes proposal by Digby Anderson to set up the Centre for the Development of Social Science.
    - "The Use of Markets in Medicine [Mercato ed intervento pubblico nel servizio sanitario]," lecture, Fondazione Luigi Einaudi conference, Rome (Italy), 1980 January 31 (Box 355, Folder 1)
      Notes, typescript and correspondence. Includes newspaper version and clippings from Italian newspapers referring to A. Seldon.
    - Lecture, Advanced Management Development Programme 5, Institute of Local Government Studies (INLOGOV), University of Birmingham (Great Britain), 1980 February 6 (Folder 2)
      Notes, program, and correspondence. See also General/Lecture notes.
    - Comment on John Methven's speech, New Zealand Employers Federation convention, Auckland (New Zealand), 1980
      Subsequently published under the title A Credo for Private Enterprise.
      - Typed notes and printed copy (Folder 3)
      - Program and conference papers (Folder 4)
      - Brochures (Folder 5)
      - Correspondence (Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous re itinerary and travel (Box 356, Folder 1)
    - "Price-Less Opinion Research," British Public Opinion, typescript and printed copy, 1980 Spring (Folder 2)
    - Lecture, Yorkshire and Humberside annual dinner, Confederation of British Industry (CBI), typescript, 1980 March 18 (Folder 3)
      Includes correspondence with and speech by John Methven. See also General/Lecture notes.
    - "Financing Education," lecture, Conservative [...] Committee on Education, notes, 1980 March 27?? (Folder 4)
    - Lecture, Builders Merchants' Federation, 1980 March 28 (Folder 5)